- 자, 다음은 챈들러
- 좋아
-Okay, Chandler.
-Okay.
네 운세는 이래
And your horoscope says:
5일, 특별한 사람에게서
선물을 받는다
"On the 5th, a special
someone will give you a gift."
오, 미리 고마워
Well, thank you in advance.
"But the 12th brings a lover's spat."
12일엔 연인과 다툰다는데?
내 선물을 두고
또 비아냥거렸구나
You're going to make fun
of my present.
왜 이러는 거야?
Why would you do that?
잠깐, 19일엔 누군가
짝사랑을 고백한다
Wait. "On the 19th,
a secret crush announces itself."
- 얘들아
- 어서 와
-Hey, guys.
-Hey.
어머나! '맥과 치즈'의
조이 트리비아니잖아!
It's Joey Tribbiani
of Mac and C.H.E.E.S.E.
오늘이 첫날이지? 로봇과 함께
범죄에 맞서 싸우려니 떨리냐?
That's right. It's your first day.
Are you psyched to fight crime
with your robot sidekick?
떨리냐고?
Am I?
The lead in my own TV series?
TV드라마의 주인공이 됐어
드디어 꿈이 이루어진 거야
I've dreamed about this for years!
근데 난 준비가 안 됐어
Why have I not been preparing?
걱정 마, 잘할 수 있을 거야
You're gonna be great.
로봇이랑 연기해야 되는데
내가 과학에 대해서 뭘 아냐
But I gotta act with a robot.
I know nothing about technology.
포르노 볼 거 아니면
챈들러 컴퓨터도 안 써
I can't even use Chandler's computer,
except to find porn.
그것도 전원만 올리면
바로 나오니까 보지만
And that's only because
it's there when you turn it on.
Our spat will start early this month.
연인과의 다툼이
좀 일찍 시작되겠다
내가 기다릴게
I'll be waiting.
The One Where Ross Meets Elizabeth's Dad
Are you judging them by their covers?
You're really not supposed to.
표지로 책을 평가하니?
그래선 안 되는 거야
I'm deciding which one to use. I'm
going to write another book.
한 가지를 골라야 돼
또 책을 쓸 생각이거든
마지막 작품이
그렇게 많이 팔렸어?
Because the last one
was such a big seller?
If you must know,
I have written 14 books.
난 지금까지 14권의 책을 썼어
And as I'm the only one
who has read them...
그걸 읽은 유일한 독자로서
자신 있게 말하는데
I can tell you that
they have been well received.
모두 좋은 평가를 받았어
근데 불이 나서 다 타버렸잖아
But I lost all of them in the fire.
So this one I'm gonna keep in an
asbestos-lined box far away from Rachel.
이건 레이첼 손이 안 닿는
석면박스에 보관할 거야
Who I forgive.
다 용서했네요
얘들아
- 그래
- 어서 와
What are you doing later?
너희들 오늘 할 일 있냐?
난 레이첼이랑
미용실에 갈 거야
Rachel and I have to get our hair cut.
그래?
-We do?
-I wanna see what he wants.
일단 달아날 구멍이야
Elizabeth's dad wants to meet me.
엘리자베스의 아빠가
날 보자고 하신대
잠깐, 거기서 대기
Wait a minute. Hold the phone.
네가 엘리자베스 아빠 아니냐?
You're not Elizabeth's dad?
That's the only one you get.
그거 하나밖에 생각 안 나지?
날 무지 싫어하셔
And he hates me.
He asked Elizabeth why she'd want
to go out with a guy...
또래 여자도 못 사귀는 남자를
만나서 뭐하냐는 거지
who couldn't get a girl his own age.
그래서 걔는 뭐랬대?
And what did she say to that?
And that's yours.
넌 그거냐?
농담할 때가 아냐
정말 잘 보이고 싶어
Come on. I really want
this guy to like me.
It would really help if you guys
could make me look good.
너희가 얘기만 잘해주면
큰 도움이 될 거야
- 그래, 도와줄게
- 우리만 믿어
-Of course we'll help.
-Thanks.
고맙다
We know how tough those
parent-teacher conferences can be.
그래, 학부모 면담이 얼마나
어려운지 우리도 잘 알지
여기가 사무실 세트예요
-So here's your office set.
-Wow!
Mac Machiavelli, private investigator.
사립탐정 맥 마키아벨리입니다
이건 내가 다 읽은 책이군요
Look at all the books I've read.
좋습니다
이제 의상 가봉하러 가죠
Let's get you to wardrobe.
근데 로봇은 언제 볼 수 있죠?
When do I meet the robot?
그걸 잊었군요
저기 있습니다
Right now. He's right here.
Joey Tribbiani, this is..
- 조이 트리비아니, 이쪽은...
- 세상에
Wow! He's so lifelike.
진짜 사람 같네
Unbelievable.
- 감쪽같아요
- 웨인이에요
This is Wayne, the man who created
and operates C.H.E.E.S.E.
치즈를 제작하고 조종할 분이죠
How do you do there, buddy?
안녕하십니까
I'll let you two guys get acquainted.
- 두 분 얘기 나누세요
- 그러죠
죄송합니다
Sorry about that.
-So where's C.H.E.E.S.E.?
-C.H.E.E.S.E. is right here.
- 치즈는 어디 있죠?
- 치즈는 여기...
보시죠
Nice to meet you, Mac.
만나서 반가워요, 맥
저건 임시로 쓸 로봇이죠?
-This is the temporary robot, right?
-No. Why?
아뇨, 왜요?
꽤 근사한 로봇일 줄 알았거든요
I thought it was gonna be
a really cool robot.
Like the Terminator,
or when I first saw you.
터미네이터나
아까 당신 모습처럼
I spent two years developing this.
It's state of the art.
꼬박 2년 걸려 만든 겁니다
최첨단 기술이라구요
Sorry. It doesn't look like
it can do anything.
죄송합니다
좀 부실하게 생겨서
이런 것도 해요
It can do this.
옴마야
This is my father, Paul Stevens.
Dad, this is Ross Geller.
우리 아빠세요
폴 스티븐스
아빠, 이쪽은 로스 겔러
It's great to meet you, Paul.
반갑습니다, 폴
얘 남자친구들은 보통 날
스티븐스 씨라고 부르지
I prefer that Liz's boyfriends
address me as Mr. Stevens.
당연히 그래야죠
스티븐스 씨
Of course. Mr. Stevens.
So, Ross...
그래, 로스...
what's your problem?
자네 문제가 뭔가?
Excuse me?
무슨 말씀이신지
왜 또래 여자를 못 사귀나?
Why can't you get a girlfriend
your own age?
그거 재미있군요
It's funny...
It's not funny.
아뇨, 재미없습니다
- 난 자네가 영 마음에 안 들어
- 알겠습니다
I don't like you going out
with my daughter, Ross.
Okay, I can see that.
물론 그러시겠죠
하지만 한 번만 기회를 주시면
I think if you give me one chance,
I can change your mind.
생각이 바뀌실 겁니다
-Okay.
-What?
좋아
뭐가요?
좋다고, 기회를 줄 테니
내 생각을 바꿔보게
Okay. I'll give you one chance
to change my mind.
You've got one minute.
딱 1분이야
-Daddy.
-Fine. Two minutes. Go.
- 아빠
- 알았다
2분, 시작
그래...
A minute and 50 seconds.
1분 50초
좋습니다
I want you to know, I've
never done anything like this before.
저도 이런 관계는
생전 처음입니다
I mean, I've been in relationships
in general.
물론 평범한 여자관계는
여러 번 있었지만
But I've never done it with a student.
I mean, not...
제자랑 해본 적은 없습니다
제 말은 그게 아니고...
해봤다는 건 꼭 무슨 짓을
했다는 뜻이 아닙니다
Not "it." We haven't done "it."
다른 짓은 많이 해봤지만...
I mean, we've done stuff...
Okay. A joke. Lighten the mood.
네, 그럼 조크 하나 하죠
분위기도 바꿀 겸
Two guys go into a bar.
One of them is Irish.
남자 둘이 바에 갔는데
하나가 아일랜드인이었죠
-I'm Irish.
-And the Irish guy wins the joke.
내가 아일랜드사람일세
근데 아일랜드인이
조크를 해서 이겨요
- 오빠
- 로스
Ross! How crazy
that we would run into you.
어쩜 오빠를 여기서 만나네
Oh, my God! Thank you.
어서 와라, 고맙다
이쪽으로
I'd like you to meet my friends.
This is Phoebe, Monica and Chandler.
스티븐스 씨, 친구들입니다
피비, 모니카, 챈들러
피비
-Phoebe.
-Hello.
- 안녕하세요
- 반가워요
-Monica.
-Hi.
- 모니카
- 안녕하세요
챈더?
Chunder.
-Chandler.
-Never going to remember that.
챈들러입니다
- 외우기 참 힘드네
- 그렇죠
선생님이 엘리자베스의
아버지시군요
You're Elizabeth's dad?
I see where she gets her...
- 네
- 따님이 아빨 닮아서 그렇게...
rugged handsomeness.
거칠고 핸섬하군요
스티븐스 부인도 계시나요?
Is there a Mrs. Stevens?
There's a Mr. Bing!
빙 씨는 계신다
Unfortunately, Lizzie's mom passed
away after she was born.
안타깝게도 집사람은
얘를 낳고는 세상을 떴어요
I raised her by myself.
혼자 이 녀석을 키웠죠
I get that a lot.
많이 듣는 소리예요
좋아요, 그럼 다들
자리에 앉을까요?
Why don't we all take a seat?
I'll get us all some coffees.
그리고 난 가서
커피를 가져올게
Yeah, why don't you...
네, 직접 하시죠
너희는 아무 얘기나 하고 있어
Talk about
whatever you want.
Whatever pops into your head.
생각나는 건 뭐든 좋으니까
이 시간에 여기서 오빠를
보다니 정말 뜻밖이에요
It is strange seeing Ross here,
this time of day...
because usually
he's at the children's hospital.
- 보통 소아과병원에 있는데
- 네
But not looking for dates.
여자한테는 눈 안 돌리고
모니카는 교수님 여동생이에요
Monica is Ross's sister.
He's a great brother!
정말 좋은 오빠랍니다
I had a sister.
나도 여동생이 있었죠
세상을 떠났지만
She passed away.
You don't have to do that every time.
매번 그럴 거 없어요
But Ross is a great guy.
I was roommates with him in college.
로스는 참 괜찮은 친구죠
대학시절 룸메이트였어요
Funny story...
이건 우스갯소린데...
선생님 룸메이트는 죽었겠죠?
Your roommate in college died,
didn't he?
A part of him did, yes.
신체일부는 그렇게 됐어요
커피 여기 있어요
폴, 엘리자베스
Here we are, Paul, Elizabeth.
I hope you guys are finding
something to talk about.
그동안 재미있는
얘기들 좀 했어?
-Yes. We were just..
-Sorry I'm late.
- 그래, 방금...
- 늦어서 미안해
하지만 너 띄워줄
준비는 다 끝났어
But I am ready to talk you up.
-When does Liz's father get here?
-I'm already here.
엘리자베스 아빠는 언제 오신대?
벌써 왔습니다
Ross is so great!
오! 로스 진짜 괜찮아요
Hey, Phoebe.
How's the book writing going?
- 얘, 피비
- 그래
책은 잘 써져?
아주 좋아
벌써 47페이지야
Really well. I'm up to page 47.
-Wow! What are you writing?
-Page numbers.
뭘 쓰는데?
쪽수 매긴다
Honey, you got the kind
with the little girl.
여자애가 그려진 걸 샀네
아기 그림으로 산다면서
You said you'd buy the kind
with the baby.
- 아기는 징그럽다며
- 아니, 여자애가 징그러워
-You said the baby creeps you out.
-The little girl does.
- 아기랬어
- 아기가 왜 징그러워
-You said the baby.
-Why would a baby creep me out?
여자애는 왜 징그러운데?
Why would the little girl
creep you out?
미안한데 좀 천천히 말해줄래?
Can you please talk a little slower?
-This is for your book?
-It's about relationships.
우리 얘기를 쓰냐?
남녀관계에 대한 거야
기만과 함정, 주의사항
The traps, the pitfalls,
what not to do.
Keep going. This stuff's great.
계속해, 아주 좋다
뭐? 지금 뭐랬어?
Excuse me.
And how none of it matters when
the people really love each other.
진정한 사랑 앞에선 그런 게
문제가 안 된다는 내용도 있어
And how people will believe anything
as long as it's a compliment.
그리고 사람들은 칭찬이라면
무조건 믿는다는 내용까지
-Oh, hi!
-Hi.
어머, 오셨어요?
네
열쇠를 흘린 것 같아요
-I left my keys here somewhere.
-Well, let's look for them.
그럼 찾아봐야죠
어디 보자...
Hey, look! Are these them?
어라? 이건가요?
No.
아뇨
All right.
그럼 뭐
-Here they are.
-Good.
- 여기 있군요
- 다행이네요
-Thanks for your help.
-Wait! Sorry!
고마워요
잠깐 저 좀 보세요, 폴 씨
-Mr. Paul?
-Just call me Paul.
- 그냥 폴이라고 불러요
- 폴...
Paul.
I just wanted you to know that...
이건 아셨으면 좋겠어요
로스는 정말 좋은 애거든요
Ross really is a great guy.
Maybe you could date him. It'd
save me the trouble of killing him.
그럼 아가씨가 사귀든지
내가 죽이긴 싫으니까
Are you okay?
왜 그러죠?
스무 살짜리 딸이 있다고는
믿어지지 않아요
You don't look old enough
to have a 20-year-old daughter.
Well, we were very young
when we had her.
우리가 젊었을 때
그 애를 가졌으니까요
-We?
-It usually takes two people to...
우리요?
아이를 가지려면 둘이서...
네, 그렇죠
Oh, no! Yes! Of course. I know that!
제 말은 아직 '우리'인가요?
아님 그냥 '나'예요?
What I meant was are you still "we"
or are you just you?
I'm just me.
지금은 혼자죠
My wife died shortly after
Lizzie was born.
아내는 엘리자베스를 낳고
곧 세상을 떠났어요
So you raised her all on your own?
그럼 혼자서 키우신 거예요?
Yes, I did.
그런 셈이죠
-What are you writing there?
-I'm drawing a picture of you.
뭘 쓰는 거야?
자기를 그리고 있어
Well, that's very flattering.
그거 영광인데?
But it'd be great if you could draw me
with some clothes and a head.
옷도 좀 입히고
머리도 있었으면 더 좋겠다
- 나다
- 그래
- 첫날인데 어땠어?
- 좋았는데
How was your first day?
Pretty good. Except I got
attitude from the robot.
로봇 성질이 못됐더라
충성하라고 만들어놨더니
이것들은 하여간!
Damn those robots. They're supposed
to be our faithful servants!
It was the guy who controls the robot.
로봇이 아니라 조종하는
사람이 문제야, 날 싫어해
He hates me. He had C.H.E.E.S.E.
knock over the sandwich table...
내가 샌드위치를 집으려는데
로봇 시켜서 탁자를 뒤집잖아
right when I was reaching for one.
Why don't you get him fired?
그럼 해고시켜버려
그래야겠어
I may have to. I hate to do it.
But I'm the star, you know?
내키진 않지만 난 스타잖아?
안 그래? 바닥에서 샌드위치
주워 먹는 데도 한계가 있어
There's a limit to how many sandwiches
I can eat off the floor.
잠깐만
Excuse me.
Joey Tribbiani.
조이 트리비아니입니다
Joe! I'm glad I found you!
I got an audition for you.
조이, 얼마나 찾았는데
오디션 잡아놨어
일종의 비공식 오디션인데
But it's kind of on the q.t.
지금 역을 맡은 배우가
조만간 짤린다는 거야
The actor who has the part
doesn't know he might be fired.
시리즈 주인공이거든
It's the lead in a series.
'맥과 치즈'
Mac and C.H.E.E.S.E.
I'm the lead in Mac and C.H.E.E.S.E.
거기 주인공이 저예요
조이?
Joey?
Hi, Ross.
어서 오게, 로스
I was just getting him to like you.
너 좋아하게 만드는 중이야
조이?
Joey!
조이!
조이 집에 없어
Ross, Joey is not here.
I'll just wait for him in here!
그럼 여기서 기다릴게
Ross, it's okay. You can come out.
로스, 괜찮아
나와도 돼
괜찮다니까, 날세
Yeah. It's okay. It's me...
미스터 스티븐스
Mr. Stevens.
I didn't... Oh, my gosh.
I didn't even see you.
저런, 미처 누구신지
몰라봤네요
왜 이래
You did. You came in, got all awkward
and ran to the bedroom.
어색하니까 들어가면서
이랬잖아, '조이! 조이!'
You were shouting, "Joey!"
- 잘 있어요, 레이첼
- 안녕히 가세요
-Bye, Rachel.
-Bye.
I'll call you later.
- 전화할게요
- 네, 또 봐요
-See you.
-Bye, Ross.
나 가네
What? What the..? How did...? What?
이게, 대체, 뭐가
어떻게, 어쩌다가...
열쇠를 잃어버려서
그걸 찾으러 왔더라고
You know, he lost his keys.
So he was looking for them.
네 입으로?
In your mouth?
아니
No!
아래층에 와서 두 시간쯤
얘길 했는데 맘에 들어서
Downstairs. And we got to talking...
for two hours. I liked him.
I invited him for coffee.
커피 한잔 대접한 거야
커피하우스에선 뭐하고!
You were at the coffeehouse!
What's the big deal?
So I kissed the guy.
내가 죽을죄라도 졌니?
그래, 키스 좀 했다
내 여자친구의 아빠야
He is my girlfriend's father.
It's weird!
이건 너무 이상하잖아
넌 내 동생도 만났어
-You dated my sister!
-That was different!
- 그건 경우가 달라
- 뭐? 왜?
-What? Why?
-This is weird for me!
내 느낌이 이상하니까
로스, 들어봐
너한테도 잘된 일이야
Ross, look. This is good for you.
Let's face it.
So far the guy's not loving you.
현실적으로 생각하자
지금 폴은 널 안 좋아해
But I can turn that around.
I've got the inside track.
내가 바꿔놓을 수 있어
확 휘어잡았거든
다같이 외식하러 가서
널 띄워줄 수도 있고
We could all go out to dinner.
And I could talk you up.
게다가 저 사람은 대단히
잘나가는 변호사야
Plus the guy
is a very successful lawyer.
-How is that important?
-It's important!
- 그게 왜 중요해?
- 엄청 중요하지
결국 맥 역을 맡길 배우는
길에 널렸다는 얘긴데
There's a million guys
who can play Mac...
and there's one robot.
로봇은 한 대고 그걸 조종하는
사람도 딱 한 명이야
And this one guy who controls it.
I didn't know he could get me fired.
오히려 그 친구가 날 해고할
상황이야, 어떡하면 좋지?
-What am I gonna do?
-You're a pretty charming guy.
조이, 넌 매력적인 애잖아
Thanks. But I have a problem
to deal with.
고맙다만 지금은
다른 얘기 중이거든?
No, you've got to win over
the guy who controls C.H.E.E.S.E.
그 로봇 조종하는 남자를
네 편으로 만들라는 거야
잘난 로봇박사 엉덩이에
키스를 퍼부어 버려
Go back there
and kiss some serious robot ass!
That's not a bad idea!
그거 괜찮은 생각이다
If I have to be charming tomorrow,
I'm not wasting it on you guys.
내일부터 발산할 내 매력을
너희한테 낭비해선 안 되지
I got some saved for you, Phoebe.
널 위해서는 조금
남겨둘게, 피비
Do you think Joey is
more charming than me?
조이가 나보다 더 매력적인가?
그럼, 그래서 가끔
조이하고도 자거든
Yeah. That's why I'm sleeping
with him on the side.
희망사항이겠지
You wish.
"You wish."
희망사항...
우리 얘기 그만 써
Stop writing about us.
I'm not writing about you.
I'm writing about other people.
너희 얘기 쓰는 거 아냐
다른 사람 얘기 쓰는 거야
-Who?
-Marsha and Chester.
누구?
마샤와 체스터
그래, 좋아
Fine. Then you know what?
I will just write about Phyllis.
이제부터 우리도
'필리스'에 대해 쓸 거야
-"Phyllis is sitting in the chair."
-I see what you're doing.
'필리스가 의자에 앉아있다'
무슨 뜻인지 알겠어
"Phyllis sees what I'm doing."
'필리스가 무슨 뜻인지 알았다'
내가 하던 짓을 남한테서
당하니까 너무 찝찝해
I have tasted my own medicine
and it is bitter!
Morning!
안녕하세요
How's my favorite genius
and his robot?
천재박사님과 로봇친구는
오늘 어떠신가요?
- 만지지 말아요
- 알았어요
-Don't touch him!
-Okay.
Level with me. I keep hearing
rumors that I might get fired.
웨인, 까놓고 얘기합시다
내가 짤릴 거란
소문이 파다해요
They even have actors reading
for my part.
심지어 내 역할 맡기려고
오디션도 진행 중이라는데
제발 한번만 더 기회를 줘요
Come on. You gotta give me
a second chance.
I love this little guy.
난 얘가 너무 좋은데...
이래서 만지지 말라고 했군요
자, 받으세요
That's why you didn't want me
to touch him, right?
빌어먹을, 돌겠네
I can't believe it. God!
젠장
Hey, how are you doing?
아가씨, 안녕하쇼
So it seemed that my prom date
had stood me up.
졸업무도회 파트너한테
바람을 맞았는데
So Ross selflessly offered to take me.
로스가 기특하게도...
절 데려가 줬어요
What a nice story.
정말 근사해요
당시 로스는 대학생이었는데
So Ross was in college...
그 틈을 타 새파란 여고생을
무도회에 데려갔다 이거군
and decided to jump at the chance
to take a young girl to her prom.
I definitely did not see
that one backfiring.
그 얘기가 오발탄이
될 줄은 정말 몰랐네
-I'm going to the bathroom.
-Take your time.
화장실 다녀올게
그래, 천천히 일봐
I was a freshman and she was a senior.
So it wasn't as bad as..
그때 전 1학년이었고 레이첼은
졸업반이라 그렇게 나쁜 건...
로스, 이보게
Look. I know I've been giving you
a lot of jabs.
내가 너무 면박만 주는 거 아네
It's partly because
I'm very protective of Lizzie...
딸을 지켜주고 싶은
보호본능도 있고
and partly because
they just keep coming to me.
자꾸 머릿속에...
그런 말이 떠오르거든
I admit after all the
wonderful things Lizzie told me...
어쨌든 우리 애가 말한
자네의 장점은 인정하네
레이첼한테서 들은
엄청난 사연도 있고
and the many, many, many stories
that Rachel has told me...
well...
뭐 자네도...
you're not...
그렇게...
all bad.
나쁜 놈은 아니더군
"Not all bad."
그렇게 나쁜 놈은 아니죠
I'm sorry I was so harsh.
But you have to understand.
그동안 심하게 군 거
이해해주게
I still look at Lizzie
like she's a 12-year-old girl.
내 눈에 이 녀석은 아직
12살짜리 꼬마거든
I know what you mean. I do that too.
무슨 말씀이신지 압니다
저도 그렇거든요
-I beg your pardon?
-I don't see her as a 12-year-old.
뭐가 어째?
아뇨, 엘리자베스를
그렇게 본다는 게 아니고
저도 6살 난 아들이 있는데
제 눈엔 갓난아기 같거든요
I mean, I have a son who is 6
and I still think of him as a baby.
-A son?
-My ex-wife and I share custody of Ben.
아들이 있어?
네, 이혼한 아내와
함께 기르고 있죠
Incidentally, Carol and I
are on excellent terms...
캐롤과는 확실히 끝났습니다
선생님 부부처럼 말이죠
as I'm sure you are with your wife.
죄송합니다
I'm sorry.
It's unbelievable!
나 왜 이러는 거지?
Don't worry. I didn't realize
you were married.
됐네, 이혼한 줄은
몰랐을 뿐이니까
네, 저랑 결혼했었지만 그건...
We were. But that was just a...
웬수 같은 술 때문에
저지른 실수였죠
That was just a big drunken mistake.
You're back.
너 왔구나?
You two were married?
두 사람이 결혼했었다고?
I'm sorry.
You were talking about Emily.
어머, 미안해
에밀리 얘기였니?
알았어
We said we would meet
at the coffeehouse at 6:00.
6시에 커피하우스에서
만나기로 했잖아
7시였어
We said 7:00.
We said 6:00!
6시라니까
The only way that I said 6:00...
내가 6시란 말을 했다면
would be if I said the sentence,
"Let's meet at 7:00, not at 6:00."
이 경우 뿐이야
'7시에 만나자'
'6시 말고'
If I had said 7:00, I would have said:
내가 7시라고 했다면
이런 거겠지
"My boyfriend is such a
wiseass. 7:00!"
'와우! 내 남자 잔머리
하나는 끝내 줘, 7시래'
-Hi!
-Oh, my good God!
- 얘들아
- 돌아가시겠네
-I know what time you said.
-What?
- 난 몇 시인지 알아
- 몇 신데?
엄밀히 말하면 체스터랑
마샤가 약속한 시간이지
Well, I know what time
Chester and Marsha said.
What time?
몇 시냐고
이거 상황 대역전이구만
돌연 내 책이 참고서가 되다니
Interesting turn of events.
Suddenly it's my book to the rescue.
Let's see.
보자...
Very interesting.
아주 재미있는데?
Well this certainly clears things up.
이걸로 모든 게 분명해졌어
What does it say?
뭐라고 적었는데?
책 써줘서 고맙다고 하면
말해줄게
I will tell you as soon as you thank
me for writing my book.
Thank you for writing your book.
It's a great book...
책 써줘서 고맙다
정말 굉장한 책이구나
넌 못하는 게 없는 여왕이야
and you are the
queen of everything.
Thanks. So are you.
고마워, 너도 그래
I told you I should
not wear this color.
이 색깔 안 입는다고 했잖아
좋아, 모니카...
"Monica.. Marsha and Chester are
planning on seeing a movie Sunday.
마샤와 체스터는
일요일 밤에 영화를 보기로 했다
마샤는 6시라고 생각했고
체스터는 7시라고 생각했다
"Marsha thinks they're meeting at
6:00. Chester thinks it's 7:00."
-You knew we were gonna miss the movie?
-Right.
그럼 우리가 영화 시간
놓칠 걸 알고 있었어?
그래
Instead of telling us, you decided
to write it in your stupid book?
우리한테 말은 안 해주고
그걸 적어놓기만 했어?
마샤와 체스터는
필리스한테 화났다
"Marsha and Chester
are mad at Phyllis."
I can't believe
I'm gonna lose this job.
또 짤리다니 내가 미친다
정말 유감이다
내가 도와줄 거 있냐?
I'm so sorry, man.
Is there anything I can do?
그래, 저 미니냉장고
경비 몰래 가져갈 거야
Help me get this mini-fridge
past the security guard.
Joey, I want to talk to you.
조이, 우리 얘기 좀 합시다
난 얘기하고 싶지 않수다
I don't want to talk to you.
꼴도 보기 싫어요
내 인생 물어내쇼
I hate you. You ruined my life.
- 챈들러, 이쪽은 웨인이야
- 안녕하세요
-Chandler, Wayne. Wayne, Chandler.
-Hi.
조이, 날 도와주면
일자리를 돌려줄게요
I'll get you your job back
if you help me out.
내가 왜 당신을 돕죠?
Why should I help you out?
-The reason he just said.
-What do you need?
방금 말했잖아
뭐가 필요한데요?
전에 그 예쁜 아가씨랑
얘기하는 거 봤어요
I saw you on stage talking
to that beautiful woman.
You know, Sarah.
I wish I could talk to her.
알죠? 사라
나도 그 여자랑
얘기하고 싶어요
-Are you in love with her?
-Yeah.
그 여자 맘에 들어요?
네, 그 여자도 좋고
여자면 누구라도 괜찮아요
Her. All of them. Anyone.
Yeah. I've been there, my friend.
나도 그 심정 알죠
Listen, I guarantee you
keep your job...
여자한테 말 거는 법 알려주면
이번 역은 내가 보장할게요
if you can teach me to talk
to women like you do.
글쎄요, 웨인
You can't teach it.
It's something you're born with.
그건 배운다고 되는 게 아니라
타고나는 재주인데...
You can teach it.
I can show you right now.
물론 당장 가르쳐 드려야죠
정말인가요?
-Really?
-Sure. Yeah. I taught him.
그럼요, 얘도 가르쳤어요
Yeah. You should see the woman I'm with,
way out of my league.
지금 내 여자 보면
깜짝 놀랄 겁니다
원한다면 그 여자도 대령하죠
In fact, if you want, I can get you her.
하지만 로스는 결혼할 때마다
뭔가를 한 가지씩 배웠어요
Well, if you think about it...
Ross did learn something
from each marriage.
어떡하면 더 빨리 끝장낼까?
How to make the next one even shorter?
Wait a minute. That's not fair.
그렇게 말씀하시면 안 되죠
He was married to me a hell of a lot
longer than he was to Emily.
에밀리보다는 저하고
훨씬 오래갔거든요
He just didn't tell me.
혼인사실을 숨기고
Maybe I have to pee again.
또 쉬해야겠네요
Well, this is fun.
참 즐겁구먼
So, Ross, did you kill any
of these wives?
이보게, 로스
아내를 죽인 적은 없나?
아뇨, 전...
I have had enough of this! I
care a great deal about your daughter.
더 이상은 못 참겠군요
전 따님을 진심으로 아낍니다
즐기려고 만나는 게 아니에요
And I have treated her with respect!
So if you've got a problem with me..
- 제가 정 맘에 안 드시면..
- 지금 나한테 대드나?
-Are you yelling at me?
-God, no.
당치도 않습니다
You know what?
If you don't like Ross, that's fine.
들어보세요
아빠가 싫어도 할 수 없어요
It doesn't matter.
I'm going out with him anyway.
전 신경 안 써요
어쨌든 계속 만날 거니까
Really?
진심이냐?
Well, if it doesn't matter to her...
엘리자베스가 상관없다면
저도 그렇습니다
it doesn't matter to me.
Still not yelling.
대드는 건 아니고요
그렇다면...
What can I say?
할말이 없군
I still don't like you.
그래도 난 자네가 싫어
I'm not so crazy
about myself right now either.
괜찮습니다, 지금 저도
제가 별로 맘에 안 드니까
- 그럼 의견일치인가?
- 네, 그런 것 같군요
-Then we agree?
-I guess so.
-Neither of us like Ross.
-I like Ross.
- 우리 둘 다 로스가 싫다?
- 전 좋아요
애들이란...
Kids!
I just thought of a story
about how nice Ross is.
잠깐만요, 로스 얘기를
하나 빼먹은 게 있어요
됐어, 지금은 우리 둘 다
로스를 싫어하거든
That's okay.
We're not liking Ross right now.
거기 대해서도 할말 많아
Well, I got a lot of those too.
네 말이 맞구나, 치즈
You were right, C.H.E.E.S.E.
물건이 오마하로
배달되지 않았죠?
-The shipment never made it to Omaha?
-You got it.
그래
And the rabbi's beard?
100 percent horsehair.
게다가 그 랍비의 수염...
100% 말총이었어
Nice catch, C.H.E.E.S.E.
잘했다, 치즈
It's your line, C.H.E.E.S.E.
네 대사잖아
Wayne! Wayne!
웨인! 웨인!